LINDSAY NEAL

2966 Francis St. #304 Kansas City, KS 66103

www.lindsaykneal.com

913 226 1398

neal1191@gmail.com

EDUCATION

University of Kansas

December

2013

Bachelor of Science in Journalism, strategic communication emphasis.

Minor in Psychology, with additional courses in Business

Johnson County Community College

December

2015

Associate of Applied Science in Web Development and Digital Media. Concentration in Desktop Publishing

OVERVIEW OF SKILLS

Create strategic planning and advertising executions; conduct and document research; write blogs and social media posts; write and produce television and radio commercials, print ads; write news releases.

Design and develop websites, create digital content (written and visual graphics). Strong knowledge of user experience design, search engine optimization and analytics.

Proficient with Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop and Dreamweaver. Experience with content management systems (Wordpress, Drupal) and front-end frameworks (Bootstrap).

Core languages: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP.

EXPERIENCE

Web Designer - SoftScience Group, Inc., 6/2015 - present

Develop core company websites and other client websites. Tasks include front-end coding, UI/UX design (wireframes/mock-ups), content development (research, writing, graphics)

Cake Artist/Owner - Sweet Nothings Cakes, 8/2009 - present

Founded a specialty cake design and production, part-time business as a creative outlet.

Barista - *Caribou Coffee*, 12/2013 - 6/2015

Worked 20 - 30 hours each week to pay for college expenses.

Bakery Assistant - *Hy-Vee*, *Inc.*, 8/2010 - 12/2013

Worked 20 - 30 hours each week to pay for college expenses.

ACTIVITIES

Lead To Read

Serve KC

JoCo DEMS

Reader, I spend one day a week reading with a 1st grader to improve basic reading skills.

Member, volunteer for non-profits such as the Ronald McDonald House, Harvesters, Giving The Basics. Communications Committee, created a blog and promotional materials (handouts and signs).